cuyana.com 2012-12-11

# Story2

Are you passionate about Cuyana’s mission? Please send an email with your resume/portfolio to [jobs@cuyana.com.](mailto:jobs@cuyana.com)

## Engineer, Generalist

Do you view writing code as art? Do you believe in developing creative and innovative products? At Cuyana, we need more than just programming monkeys. Our developers are considered a critical part of the design team. Cuyana is more than just another e-commerce site. Our goal is to redefine how customers shop online. Email us!  
We are looking for an engineer who loves developing a customer’s experience end to end. Our ideal candidate is an expert at the front end, but can understand and manage the backend when needed. If you are passionate about inventing new technical solutions and growing a business, come join our team. We promise you won’t regret it.

QUALIFICATIONS:

  * An independent thinker who makes technical decisions with the user and product’s best interests
  * Entrepreneurially minded who requires little oversight and meets deadlines
  * Proficiency with Magento, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
  * Proficiency in one or more common web languages: Java, Ruby, Python, PHP, etc.
  * Significant experience developing web applications
  * Project portfolio with shipped products is a huge plus

## SHIPPING AND RETURNS

Our goal is to give you a memorable experience and make sure you love our brand as much as we do.

## Shipping

Cuyana offers FREE ground shipping via FedEx on orders going to any destination within the United States. Please allow 3-8 business days for arrival. Orders are shipped from San Francisco.

We also offer expedited orders via Fedex 2Day delivery for $20.00.

If you need your order sooner than that, please email us at support@cuyana.com and we will get your package to you on time.

## Returns

If, for any reason, you are not 100% happy with your order, we will do everything we can to make it right.

  * Cuyana returns are easy! We gladly accept the return of any unworn Cuyana product for an exchange or a full refund within 30 days.
  * Shipping on returns/exchanges is also free! Email us at support@cuyana.com and we will send you a pre-paid packaging label.

We LOVE to talk to our customers. Please contact us if you have any questions. Our toll free number is (888) 993-9092 and our email is [support@cuyana.com](mailto:support@cuyana.com)

Cuyana, Inc. (Cuyana) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Statement. By visiting the www.Cuyana.com website and domain name, or otherwise accessing any other linked pages, features, content, products or application services offered from time to time by Cuyana in connection therewith (collectively, the Site), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

## WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT COVER?

This Privacy Statement covers Cuyana’s treatment of personally identifiable information (Personal Information) that Cuyana gathers when you access the Site and when you use Cuyana’s services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Cuyana does not own or control, or to individuals that Cuyana does not employ or manage.

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES CUYANA COLLECT?

The information we gather from customers enables us to sell our customers products and personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

Personal Information You Provide to Us:

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, gender, email address, mobile phone number, credit card and/or other payment information, IP address, browser information, username, password, time zone and any other information necessary for us to provide sell your products and otherwise provide our services. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see and communicating with you about specials, sales offers and new products.

  * Registration: In order for you to use our website, you may be required to complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your first and last name, your email address and confirmation that you are 18 years or older; provided that, you should refer to our Terms of Use for additional age restrictions. 
  * Ordering: To process your order for products and services, we require contact information (such as billing address) and credit card information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders.

Personal Information Collected Automatically:

  * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Site or use our services. Cuyana automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested.
  * Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Cuyana only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Site or services so that we can make the Site appealing to as many customers as possible and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our Site or services. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use the Site or services, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, Cuyana never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

E-mail Communications:

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from Cuyana if your computer supports this type of program. Cuyana uses this confirmation to help make emails more interesting and helpful. We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. When you receive e-mail from Cuyana, you can opt out of receiving further e-mails by emailing us at info@cuyana.com.

Information from Other Sources:

For purposes such as improving the personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors’ experiences, to learn more about their use of the Site and to improve quality. 
  * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allow you to decide on the acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Site’s most attractive features.
  * Ads appearing on the Site may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Statement covers the use of cookies by Cuyana and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## WILL CUYANA SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We anticipate that we may become affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may sell items to you through the Site. In other situations, Cuyana may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Cuyana’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

Communication in response to User Information: As part of the Site and services, you will receive from Cuyana email and other communication relating to your User Information. You acknowledge and agree that by posting such User Information, Cuyana may send you email and other communication that it determines in its sole discretion relate to your User Information.

Promotional Offers: We may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send an email with your request to info@cuyana.com.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Cuyana, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Cuyana goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Cuyana may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of Cuyana and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of Cuyana, our employees, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

## CONDITIONS OF USE

If you decide to visit the Cuyana websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of California state law.

## THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Cuyana services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Websites. These other websites are not under Cuyana control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Cuyana of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Cuyana websites are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Cuyana is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

## IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?

Your Cuyana account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

Cuyana endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, Cuyana cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Site contains links to other sites. Cuyana is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site you should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Statement only governs information collected on the Site or otherwise by Cuyana.

This Privacy Statement addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers or sellers on the Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Cuyana does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

Cuyana allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as the Site changes.

  * Real name
  * Account and user profile information
  * Credit card and/or other payment information
  * User e-mail address
  * User mobile phone number
  * Username and password
  * User preferences
  * Billing, shipping and return address information

## WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain features of the Site and services.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

You may request deletion of your Cuyana account by sending an e-mail to support@cuyana.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

## CAN CHILDREN USE CUYANA’S SERVICES?

Our site and the services available through Cuyana are not intended for children under the age of 13. Cuyana does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents’ consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child’s web experience. Cuyana recommends that parents use Internet filtering technology to supervise their kids’ access to the Internet.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

Cuyana may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when he or she uses the Site after such changes have been first posted.

## QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Site, please send us a detailed message at support@cuyana.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: August 11, 2011

Karla Gallardo

Founder & CEO at Cuyana

karla@cuyana.com

PLEASE READ THE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING THE “SITE” OR USING ANY PART OF THE SITE OR “SERVICE” (BOTH AS DEFINED BELOW). BY CLICKING ON THE "I ACCEPT" BUTTON BELOW, YOU (THE USER) AGREE TO BECOME BOUND BY THE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT UNCONDITIONALLY AGREE TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE TERMS OF USE, CLICK ON THE "CANCEL" BUTTON, AND YOU WILL NOT HAVE ANY RIGHT TO USE THE SITE.

## Acceptance of Terms.

The following terms and conditions govern all use of the Cuyana.com website (the Site) and the services available at the Site (taken together, the Service). The Service is owned and operated by Cuyana, Inc. (Cuyana). The Service is offered subject to acceptance without modification of all of the terms and conditions contained herein and all other operating rules, policies and procedures that may be published from time to time on this Site by Cuyana (collectively, the Terms of Use).

The Service is available only to individuals who are at least 18 years old, whether acting on their own behalf or as an authorized employee or representative of a corporation or other business entity. If you do not so qualify, do not attempt to register for or use the Service. Cuyana may refuse to offer the Service to any person or entity and may change its eligibility criteria, at any time, in its sole discretion.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THESE TERMS OF USE, THEN DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICE. BY VIEWING OR USING ALL OR ANY PART OF THE SERVICE, DOWNLOADING ANY MATERIALS OR BY COMPLETING THE REGISTRATION PROCESS, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ALL OF THESE TERMS OF USE.

## Changes.

Cuyana reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any of these Terms of Use at any time. It is your responsibility to check the Terms of Use periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes to the Terms of Use constitutes acceptance of those changes.

## Registration.

As a condition to using the Service, you may be required to register with Cuyana and select a password and screen name (Cuyana User ID). Your Cuyana User ID cannot be changed, so please select one carefully. You shall provide Cuyana with accurate, complete and updated registration information. Failure to do so shall constitute a breach of the Terms of Use, which may result in immediate termination of your account. You must ensure that your account with Cuyana contains (at all times) a valid email address. In addition, you shall not (i) select or use as a Cuyana User ID a name or email address of another person with the intent to impersonate that person; (ii) use as a Cuyana User ID a name or email addres subject to any rights of a person other than you without appropriate authorization; or (iii) use as a Cuyana User ID a name or email address that is otherwise offensive, vulgar or obscene. Cuyana reserves the right to refuse registration of, or cancel, a Cuyana User ID in its sole discretion. You are solely responsible for activity that occurs on your account and for maintaining the confidentiality of your Cuyana password. You shall never use another user’s account without such other user’s express permission. You shall never transfer or assign your account to any third party. You will immediately notify Cuyana in writing of any unauthorized use of your account or other account- related security breach of which you are aware.

You shall only have one (1) account with the Service (which, for clarity, means that You will not register (or attempt to register) for more than one (1) account); provided that, within such personal account with the Service you may be able to open sub-accounts.

## Fees; Payment; Return Policy.

Certain products offered by (or on behalf of) Cuyana through the Site (such as hats, scarves and/or other accesories) will require payment by you (“Products”). You shall pay all applicable fees, as described on the Site, in connection with the Products selected by you. All fees are in U.S. dollars unless stated otherwise by Cuyana on the Site. All fees are payable upon demand on a Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover credit card. Cuyana reserves the right to change its prices (and to institute new charges) for the Products at any time. Purchases by you following the posting of such changes on the Site constitutes your acceptance of any new or increased charges.

Purchases are subject to Cuyana’s Shipping and Returns Policy.

## Privacy.

Cuyana's current privacy policy is available at http://www.cuyana.com/privacy-policy (the Privacy Policy), which is incorporated by this reference. We strongly urge you to review the Privacy Policy.

## Rules and Conduct.

The Service (including without limitation, any content, documents or other information made available via the Service) is provided only for your own information purposes. Any unauthorized use of the Service, including without limitation, any commercial use (such as, for example, resale to third parties), is expressly prohibited.

As a condition of use, you promise not to use the Service for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use, or any other purpose not reasonably intended by Cuyana. You agree to abide by all applicable local, state, national and international laws and regulations.

By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree not to (a) take any action or (b) upload, post, submit or otherwise distribute or facilitate distribution of any content (including text, communications, software, images, sounds, data or other information) using any communications service or other service available on or through the Service, that:

  * s unlawful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, libelous, deceptive, fraudulent, invasive of another's privacy, tortious, obscene, profane or which otherwise violates the Terms of Use;
  * infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, right of publicity or other right of any party;
  * constitutes unauthorized or unsolicited advertising, junk or bulk e-mail ("spamming");
  * imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on Cuyana's computing, storage or communications infrastructure or attempts to gain unauthorized access to the Service, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to the Service, through password mining or otherwise;
  * contains software viruses or any other computer codes, files, or programs that are designed or intended to disrupt, damage, limit or interfere with the proper function of any software, hardware or telecommunications equipment, or to damage or obtain unauthorized access to any system, data or other information of Cuyana or any third party; or
  * harvests or collects any information from the Site; or
  * impersonates any person or entity, including any employee or representative of Cuyana.
  * Cuyana may, at its sole discretion, immediately terminate your access to the Service should your conduct fail to conform strictly with any provision of this section. 

## Third Party Sites.

The Service may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites are not under Cuyana's control, and you acknowledge that Cuyana is not responsible for the accuracy, legality, appropriateness or any other aspect of the content or function of such websites. The inclusion of any such link does not imply endorsement by Cuyana or any association with its operators.

## Proprietary Rights.

You agree that all content and materials delivered via the Service or otherwise made available by Cuyana at the Site are protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents, trade secrets or other proprietary rights and laws. Except as expressly authorized by Cuyana in writing, you agree not to sell, license, rent, modify, distribute, copy, reproduce, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, publish, adapt, edit or create derivative works from such materials or content. However, you may print or download a reasonable number of copies of the materials or content at this Site for your own informational purposes; provided, that you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained therein. Systematic retrieval of data or other content from this Site to create or compile, directly or indirectly, a collection, database or directory without written permission from Cuyana is prohibited.

Reproducing, copying or distributing any content, materials or design elements on the Site for any other purpose is strictly prohibited without the express prior written permission of Cuyana. Use of the content or materials for any purpose not expressly permitted in these Terms of Use is prohibited. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.

## Termination.

Cuyana may terminate your access to all or any part of the Service at any time, with or without cause, with or without notice, effective immediately. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service.

## No Warranties.

THE SERVICE (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL CONTENT AND PRODUCTS AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICE) IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE” AND IS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND ANY WARRANTIES IMPLIED BY ANY COURSE OF PERFORMANCE OR USAGE OF TRADE, ALL OF WHICH ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED. CUYANA, AND ITS DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, PARTNERS AND CONTENT PROVIDERS DO NOT WARRANT THAT: (A) THE SERVICE WILL BE SECURE OR AVAILABLE AT ANY PARTICULAR TIME OR LOCATION; (B) ANY DEFECTS OR ERRORS WILL BE CORRECTED; (C) ANY CONTENT OR SOFTWARE AVAILABLE AT OR THROUGH THE SERVICE IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS; OR (D) THE RESULTS OF USING THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

## Limitation of Liability.

IN NO EVENT SHALL CUYANA, NOR ITS DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, CONTRACTORS, PARTNERS, SUPPLIERS OR CONTENT PROVIDERS, BE LIABLE UNDER CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY, NEGLIGENCE OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY WITH RESPECT TO THE SERVICE (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WITH RESPECT TO ANY CONTENT OR PRODUCTS AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICE) FOR ANY: (I) SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, WHETHER OR NOT FORESEEABLE, (II) THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES, (III) BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE (REGARDLESS OF THE SOURCE OF ORIGINATION), OR (IV) DIRECT DAMAGES IN EXCESS OF (IN THE AGGREGATE) $10 (U.S.) (PROVIDED THAT, IN THE CASE OF CLAIMS RELATED TO PRODUCTS YOU PURCHASED FROM CUYANA, SUCH AMOUNT SHALL BE THE PURCHASE PRICE). SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR FOR BODILY INJURY, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

## Indemnification.

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Cuyana, its affiliates and their employees, contractors, officers, directors and representatives from all liabilities, claims and expenses, including attorneys' fees, that arise from your use or misuse of the Service.

## International Use.

Cuyana makes no representation that the Content is appropriate or available for use in locations outside the United States, and accessing the Service is prohibited from territories where such Content is illegal. If you access the Service from other locations, you do so at your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.

## Dispute Resolution.

A printed version of these Terms of Use and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. You and Cuyana agree that any cause of action arising out of or related to the Service must commence within one (1) year after the cause of action arose; otherwise, such cause of action is permanently barred.

These Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, excluding its conflicts of law rules, and the United States of America. You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any claim or action arising out of or relating to these Terms of Use or your use of this Site or Services shall be filed only in the state or federal courts located in California, USA, and you further agree and submit to the exercise of personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purpose of litigating any such claim or action. Use of the Service is not authorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms of Use, including without limitation, this section.

## Integration and Severability

These Terms of Use are the entire agreement between you and Cuyana with respect to the Service and use of this Site, and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals (whether oral, written or electronic) between you and Cuyana with respect to this Site (but excluding the use of any software which may be subject to a separate end-user license agreement). If any provision of the Terms of Use is found to be unenforceable or invalid, that provision will be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that the Terms of Use will otherwise remain in full force and effect and enforceable.

## Miscellaneous.

These Terms of Use and the Service contemplated hereunder are personal to you, and are not assignable, transferable or sublicensable by you except with Cuyana's prior written consent. Cuyana may assign, transfer or delegate any of its rights and obligations hereunder without consent. All waivers and modifications must be in a writing signed by both parties, except as otherwise provided herein. No agency, partnership, joint venture or employment relationship is created as a result of this Agreement and neither party has any authority of any kind to bind the other in any respect. In any action or proceeding to enforce rights under this Agreement, the prevailing party will be entitled to recover costs and attorneys' fees. All notices under this Agreement will be in writing and will be deemed to have been duly given when received, if personally delivered or sent by certified or registered mail, return receipt requested; when receipt is electronically confirmed, if transmitted by facsimile or e-mail; or the day after it is sent, if sent for next day delivery by recognized overnight delivery service.

## Copyright and Trademark Notices.

Unless otherwise indicated, these Terms of Use and all Content provided by Cuyana are copyright © 2011 Cuyana, Inc. All rights reserved.

“Cuyana” as well as page headers, custom graphics, buttons, images and other content on the Site, are subject to trademark, service mark, trade dress, copyright and or other proprietary or intellectual property rights or licenses held by Cuyana, Inc. or its licensors, supplier or partners. Other trademarks, product names and company names or logos used on the Site are the property of their respective owners. Except as expressly authorized, the use or misuse of any trademarks, trade names, logos, images, graphics or content from the Site is strictly prohibited.

## Contact.

You may contact Cuyana at: legal@cuyana.com

Please use the form below to submit your query.  
Alternatively you can contact us on our toll free number (888) 993-9092.

Please use the form below to submit your query.  
Alternatively you can contact us on our toll free number **(888) 993-9092**.
